[
  {
    "index": 0,
     "question": "Sunset next to…",
     "answer": "Bad",
     "description": "It's terrible when the sun sets next to us"
   },
   {
     "index": 1,
     "question": "Unable to save the book in…",
     "answer": "Sir",
     "description": "Dimas borrowed his book yesterday afternoon."
   },
   {
     "index": 2,
     "question": "United we stand, divided we——-",
     "answer": "Sad",
     "description": "Who is not sad to divorce his wife??"
   },
   {
     "index": 3,
     "question": "Food wrapped in banana leaves?",
     "answer": "London",
     "description": "Easy right? Do you like lontong?"
   },
   {
     "index": 4,
     "question": "If you drive a car you must bring it",
     "answer": "One",
     "description": "If you bring 2 how do you drive it"
   },
   {
     "index": 5,
     "question": "All roses and jasmine…",
     "answer": "Flower",
     "description": "If it's not a flower, what is it, animal?"
   },
   {
     "index": 6,
     "question": "Don't throw tissues in…",
     "answer": "Place",
     "description": "Still in place why was it removed"
   },
   {
     "index": 7,
     "question": "When _____ people usually eat.",
     "answer": "Angry",
     "description": "Are people angry or not, of course they eat.."
   },
   {
     "index": 8,
     "question": "Birds are animals that can..",
     "answer": "Friend",
     "description": "Don't you fly together with your friends?"
   },
   {
     "index": 9,
     "question": "Animals that open their mouths wide",
     "answer": "Kenaflu",
     "description": "That's because you can't breathe, your nose is blocked.."
   },
   {
     "index": 10,
     "question": "An animal that changes color when there is an enemy?",
     "answer": "Bewildered",
     "description": "Because, the enemy is stunned to see the animal change color"
   },
   {
     "index": 11,
     "question": "A female artist with a thin mustache",
     "answer": "Ihkumisan",
     "description": "Why do you have a mustache?"
   },
   {
     "index": 12,
     "question": "The normal door is at….",
     "answer": "Press",
     "description": "If you normally go to the atm, the pin is pressed"
   },
   {
     "index": 13,
     "question": "Lebak bulus",
     "answer": "Famous",
     "description": "Because of Lebak Bulus, everyone knows that Cililitan is famous"
   },
   {
     "index": 14,
     "problem": "A bullfighter can be injured by being rammed..",
     "answer": "Biskota",
     "description": "You want a bull, you want a city bus, you still can get hurt.."
   },
   {
     "index": 15,
     "question": "If you wipe the mirror it becomes…",
     "answer": "Mirror",
     "description": "Yes, times change, yes, they remain mirrors"
   },
   {
     "index": 16,
     "question": "Batik is an original product from…",
     "answer": "Human",
     "description": "So far no other creature has been able to"
   },
   {
     "index": 17,
     "question": "What kind of vehicle do taxi drivers use?",
     "answer": "Strike",
     "description": "Motor really likes to stall"
   },
   {
     "index": 18,
     "problem": "What animal can't move?",
     "answer": "Pope",
     "description": "If the game is paused(e) it will stop playing"
   },
   {
     "index": 19,
     "question": "After exercise",
     "answer": "Drinking water",
     "description": "After exercising you must be thirsty right"
   },
   {
     "index": 20,
     "question": "In the wind flutters in every country",
     "answer": "clothes",
     "description": "In every country people dry their clothes"
   },
   {
     "index": 21,
     "question": "If you are thirsty, drink",
     "answer": "No",
     "description": "Just drink it later it won't wear out"
   },
   {
     "index": 22,
     "question": "What makes it smell good",
     "answer": "Pfffht",
     "description": "The sound of air freshener pffht"
   },
   {
     "index": 23,
     "question": "Hayam wuruk rules the kingdom?",
     "answer": "Oldman",
     "description": "Yes, yes… today's era"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 24,
     "question": "What is the most beautiful night?",
     "answer": "Your Night",
     "description": "Eaa…eaa…eaa.."
   },
   {
     "index": 25,
     "question": "Indonesian special food made from soybeans that is worldwide",
     "answer": "Delicious",
     "description": "A delicious and nutritious tempeh indeed"
   },
   {
     "index": 26,
     "question": "Animals live in the fields",
     "answer": "Stubborn",
     "description": "The leech lives in the river and likes to suck people's blood. Yes, it's a stubborn name"
   },
   {
     "index": 27,
     "question": "Food must be in….",
     "answer": "Cook",
     "description": "Try eating uncooked rice"
   },
   {
     "index": 28,
     "question": "Capital of Indonesia",
     "answer": "Udahada",
     "description": "What doesn't exist yet is the capital city of Jakarta"
   },
   {
     "index": 29,
     "question": "There is a bridge in Palembang...",
     "answer": "Drop",
     "description": "It's called a bridge, it can just be damaged."
   },
   {
     "index": 30,
     "question": "Let people do sports...",
     "answer": "Inlah",
     "description": "Don't ban things if people want to be healthy."
   },
   {
     "index": 31,
     "question": "Mother sewed with a needle and...",
     "answer": "Serious",
     "description": "Yes, you have to be serious, let's finish."
   },
   {
     "index": 32,
     "question": "Words to greet Batak people in Medan",
     "answer": "Hello",
     "description": "If you don't reply, it means you're busy, sis."
   },
   {
     "index": 33,
     "question": "The iron bird is also called..",
     "answer": "Order",
     "description": "Those who ordered the bird. asked for it to be made of iron"
   },
   {
     "index": 34,
     "question": "The well is shaped?",
     "answer": "Hole",
     "description": "There must be a hole if there isn't a hole it's not a well"
   },
   {
     "index": 35,
     "question": "A sign that a cat is angry with its tail?",
     "answer": "One",
     "description": "Because if not one name is not a cat"
   },
   {
     "index": 36,
     "question": "What fruit do you usually bring when you are playing at your boyfriend's house?",
     "answer": "Apple",
     "description": "Yes, if you play at your boyfriend's house, you often have apples, don't you?"
   },
   {
     "index": 37,
     "question": "Someone keeps clothes in…",
     "answer": "Anyone",
     "description": "If mom keeps it in the cupboard, if other people know where..
  },
  {
    "indexes": 38,
     "question": "What fruits are old",
     "answer": "Cassava",
     "description": "Kan si – ngkong how si vrohh"
   },
   {
     "index": 39,
     "question": "Not good at studies",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "Lessons are not smart, you can't study them"
   },
   {
     "index": 40,
     "question": "Animals with big names",
     "answer": "Fat",
     "description": "Because animals with big bodies must be fat"
   },
   {
     "index": 41,
     "question": "It's at the end of the story..",
     "answer": "Sign",
     "description": "Really? There's a t and a"
   },
   {
     "index": 42,
     "question": "Primary school is school",
     "answer": "Peace",
     "description": "May all schools be peaceful, students excel"
   },
   {
     "index": 43,
     "question": "If you are thirsty, drink",
     "answer": "Cook",
     "description": "The food is not yet cooked, so it must be cooked first"
   },
   {
     "index": 44,
     "question": "Put a flag on…",
     "answer": "Pull",
     "description": "If it's not drawn it won't raise the flag"
   },
   {
     "index": 45,
     "question": "The road is wide and you can't get through",
     "answer": "Spit",
     "description": "I've tried it myself, it's hard…"
   },
   {
     "index": 46,
     "question": "Before drinking coffee in",
     "answer": "Mouth",
     "description": "Be sure to put it in your mouth before you drink it"
   },
   {
     "index": 47,
     "question": "Nobita's friend..",
     "answer": "A few",
     "description": "Just try to count how many there are, a few, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 48,
     "question": "Let's take a shower…",
     "answer": "Byuur",
     "description": "Segeerr, have you showered yet?"
   },
   {
     "index": 49,
     "question": "The Jakarta Monument",
     "answer": "Hard",
     "description": "Just try to bite"
   },
   {
     "index": 50,
     "question": "What's the biggest chicken?",
     "answer": "Chicken universe",
     "description": "That's really big!"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 51,
     "question": "Wind instruments..",
     "answer": "Already exists",
     "description": "There are already a lot of types, you know."
   },
   {
     "index": 52,
     "question": "In the library may not..",
     "answer": "Shampoo",
     "description": "Later the book will all get wet.."
   },
   {
     "index": 53,
     "question": "Rizky febian was born in",
     "answer": "Shoot",
     "description": "Yes, when you carry it, it's time to bathe it right away"
   },
   {
     "index": 54,
     "question": "Warriors fight invaders with weapons??",
     "answer": "Make Your Own",
     "description": "If you don't make it yourself, then who will make it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 55,
     "question": "Brother took sister to school to school",
     "answer": "Tired",
     "description": "Carrying her in my arms"
   },
   {
     "index": 56,
     "question": "Sick people drink?",
     "answer": "Oya",
     "description": "It hurts to drink a lot of it, let me get well soon"
   },
   {
     "index": 57,
     "question": "The plane landed at…",
     "answer": "Help",
     "description": "Pilot, co-pilot, airport operator, etc.."
   },
   {
     "index": 58,
     "question": "There is a younger sibling at home",
     "answer": "Cook",
     "description": "Hmm, what do you think I'm cooking now…"
   },
   {
     "index": 59,
     "question": "The number plate of vehicle a comes from?",
     "answer": "Samsat",
     "description": "Because Samsat is an institution that has the right to issue motorized vehicle plates."
   },
   {
     "index": 60,
     "question": "Heavy rain makes …",
     "answer": "Wet",
     "description": "When it's hot it's dry"
   },
   {
     "index": 61,
     "question": "It is recommended to eat with your hands…",
     "correct answer",
     "description": "You can go right or left, right is better," he said.
   },
   {
     "index": 62,
     "question": "What is not allowed to take on an airplane",
     "answer": "Alone",
     "description": "Because if we bring it ourselves it will fall"
   },
   {
     "index": 63,
     "question": "Avocado",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "It can be called"
   },
   {
     "index": 64,
     "question": "Ex-boyfriend mentioned",
     "answer": "Don't",
     "description": "Later the current girlfriend is angry"
   },
   {
     "index": 65,
     "question": "There are 10 fish dead and 2 left in the aquarium",
     "answer": "Discarded",
     "description": "If you don't throw it away, the other fish will die too"
   },
   {
     "index": 66,
     "question": "Not coming to work due to the day...",
     "answer": "Diphk",
     "description": "Yes, one day, if you get laid off, you don't have to go back to work..."
   },
   {
     "index": 67,
     "question": "Tinky winky",
     "answer": "Extremely",
     "description": "The name is well known in all circles"
   },
   {
     "index": 68,
     "question": "The lizard fell to…",
     "answer": "Bacok",
     "description": "I fell stabbed"
   },
   {
     "index": 69,
     "question": "Your mouth ………..",
     "answer": "Only one",
     "description": "You only have one mouth"
   },
   {
     "index": 70,
     "question": "What causes thirst during Ramadan",
     "answer": "Weather",
     "description": "If it's hot, it'll make you thirsty, if you're fasting, you'll be hungry too…"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 71,
     "question": "Send money via ATM?",
     "answer": "Thanks",
     "description": "Thanks, accepted"
   },
   {
     "index": 72,
     "question": "Birds fly with?",
     "answer": "anything",
     "description": "Yes, the cat flies.."
   },
   {
     "index": 73,
     "question": "There is a shrimp behind…",
     "answer": "Gnadu",
     "description": "That's a fact"
   },
   {
     "index": 74,
     "question": "What kind of ice can walk",
     "answer": "Escalator",
     "description": "If it doesn't work, it's not an ice calator but a calator ladder"
   },
   {
     "index": 75,
     "question": "Your heart is happy even though you don't have one",
     "answer": "Glass",
     "description": "Glass is also not very important"
   },
   {
     "index": 76,
     "question": "Husband, bu camat?",
     "answer": "male",
     "description": "Because if you're not a lesbian, it's a sin…"
   },
   {
     "index": 77,
     "question": "You don't know then you don't",
     "answer": "Invite",
     "description": "People who don't know how to cook are invited"
   },
   {
     "index": 78,
     "question": "Animals howling at night…",
     "answer": "Trapped on",
     "description": "Too bad he got stepped on"
   },
   {
     "index": 79,
     "question": "Fire is held feels?",
     "answer": "Difficult",
     "description": "Fire is hard to hold, it gets hot again"
   },
   {
     "index": 80,
     "question": "In a game of badminton",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "Try watching badminton, I'm sure the Indonesian name is abbreviated"
   },
   {
     "index": 81,
     "question": "There is a bolster there is…",
     "answer": "Thread",
     "description": "If you don't have sewing thread, what do you use?"
   },
   {
     "index": 82,
     "question": "Andi got drenched because?",
     "answer": "Husen",
     "description": "Because husen threw it into the pool, it was really naughty…"
   },
   {
     "index": 83,
     "question": "Sunset day starts",
     "answer": "Go home",
     "description": "It's too late if you don't come home, the day your mother looks for you"
   },
   {
     "index": 84,
     "question": "To be clean we bathe with……..",
     "answer": "Sure",
     "description": "If you're not sure better don't take a shower……."
   },
   {
     "index": 85,
     "question": "People walk on water without using it",
     "answer": "Brain",
     "description": "You already know there are roads why you have to walk on water"
   },
   {
     "index": 86,
     "question": "A child learns so that…",
     "answer": "Kanaja",
     "description": "If it's banned, it won't be smart"
   },
   {
     "index": 87,
     "question": "Animals that eat everything?",
     "answer": "Greed",
     "description": "Everything is eaten"
   },
   {
     "index": 88,
     "question": "Birds fly using..",
     "answer": "Spirit",
     "description": "If you don't get excited, you will get weak.."
   },
   {
     "index": 89,
     "question": "Buy lights usually at",
     "answer": "Try",
     "description": "If you buy a lamp, you must try it first"
   },
   {
     "index": 90,
     "question": "Don't be friends with people",
     "answer": "Missing",
     "description": "How do I…"
   },
   {
     "index": 91,
     "question": "People crossing the river are usually built…",
     "answer": "Run",
     "description": "Why don't people cross the road?"
   },
   {
     "index": 92,
     "question": "When are you usually hungry?",
     "answer": "Lazy",
     "description": "Because you don't have the power, you're lazy"
   },
   {
     "index": 93,
     "question": "Diligent base…",
     "answer": "Got",
     "description": "If you don't work hard, you won't get results"
   },
   {
     "index": 94,
     "question": "State-owned enterprises can be abbreviated as ….",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "Can you shorten it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 95,
     "question": "tiles are made because",
     "answer": "Need",
     "description": "If you don't need anything to make tiles"
   },
   {
     "index": 96,
     "question": "Answer correctly. the world consists of five …",
     "correct answer",
     "description": "I told you to answer correctly"
   },
   {
     "index": 97,
     "question": "If you want to take the train, you usually go to…",
     "answer": "Anterin",
     "description": "Yes, I'll take you to the station, whether it's a relative, friend, or motorcycle taxi driver."
   },
   {
     "index": 98,
     "question": "Do you brush your teeth before?",
     "answer": "break",
     "description": "If it's broken it's hard to scrub it"
   },
   {
     "index": 99,
     "question": "People are confused thinking",
     "answer": "Very long",
     "description": "Yeah..like you"
   },
   {
     "index": 100,
     "question": "Cockroach",
     "answer": "Different",
     "description": "If you call it the same, ants..ants..ants.."
  },
  {
    "index": 101,
     "question": "Indonesia's first president",
     "answer": "One",
     "description": "Definitely one"
   },
   {
     "index": 102,
     "question": "People usually send letters in…",
     "answer": "Pocket",
     "description": "Pocketed first, then to the post office"
   },
   {
     "index": 103,
     "question": "The difference between goats and sheep",
     "answer": "Little",
     "description": "Just different feathers coy"
   },
   {
     "index": 104,
     "question": "Assembling upstream",
     "answer": "River",
     "description": "Actually I can go to the lake, but I want the river again."
   },
   {
     "index": 105,
     "question": "Exercise makes the body…",
     "wrong answer",
     "description": "Yes exercise makes the body, yes wrong !!"
   },
   {
     "index": 106,
     "question": "The first to discover the Americas",
     "answer": "Not me",
     "description": "Well, it's not me, who discovered Columbus..."
   },
   {
     "index": 107,
     "question": "What a sad night",
     "answer": "Evening",
     "description": "Yes, like you..don't be sad…puk..puk.."
   },
   {
     "index": 108,
     "question": "One plus one..",
     "answer": "Two",
     "description": "Just like that it's hard.."
   },
   {
     "index": 109,
     "question": "Sma is a middle school..",
     "answer": "Secure",
     "description": "If it's not safe, it's not a school.."
   },
   {
     "index": 110,
     "question": "What do people do when they are sick?",
     "answer": "Go home",
     "description": "It's true that you're going home... you're sick, what are you going to do?"
   },
   {
     "index": 111,
     "question": "Who likes to eat bananas?",
     "answer": "Many",
     "description": "Not only monkeys who like it, do any of you like it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 112,
     "question": "Ahead of Eid we are not required to buy?",
     "answer": "Nail",
     "description": "Why buy nails, better buy clothes"
   },
   {
     "index": 113,
     "question": "What blue bones come on…",
     "answer": "Stone",
     "description": "The color is blue isn't it"
   },
   {
     "index": 114,
     "question": "Before flying, pilots usually...",
     "answer": "Bye",
     "description": "So that I don't look for it.."
   },
   {
     "index": 115,
     "question": "Friends that are hard to find are common again",
     "answer": "Pdkt",
     "description": "Cieee eee cieee"
   },
   {
     "index": 116,
     "question": "Turtle flipped over?",
     "answer": "Poor",
     "description": "I'm sorry I won't come back later"
   },
   {
     "index": 117,
     "question": "Ten plus six equals six……",
     "wrong answer",
     "description": "Ten plus six ko six"
   },
   {
     "index": 118,
     "question": "The car cannot go forward because…",
     "answer": "Parking",
     "description": "Why are cars parked in progress anyway"
   },
   {
     "index": 119,
     "question": "Animal name repeated..",
     "answer": "Rarely",
     "description": "Rarely try to mention.."
   },
   {
     "index": 120,
     "question": "Running is making",
     "wrong answer",
     "description": "Run, run, make, make.."
  },
  {
    "indexes": 121,
     "question": "What eggs are often afraid of..",
     "answer": "Telorasin",
     "description": "Look at the tattoo, it makes me cringe,"
   },
   {
     "index": 122,
     "question": "What is available at Padang Restaurant",
     "answer": "Cash",
     "description": "So there's a change, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 123,
     "question": "Indonesia is a country with land?",
     "answer": "Airbeta",
     "description": "Freedom.."
   },
   {
     "index": 124,
     "question": "Not found",
     "answer": "Stolen",
     "description": "Thieves are rude"
   },
   {
     "index": 125,
     "question": "Those who break the fast",
     "answer": "Azan",
     "description": "I thought it was already Maghrib prayer, but it's still noon"
   },
   {
     "index": 126,
     "question": "Animals in the zoo",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "Yes, correct that animals are in the zoo"
   },
   {
     "index": 127,
     "question": "What is the function of brakes?",
     "answer": "speeding",
     "description": "Try it without brakes. Do you dare to speed?"
   },
   {
     "index": 128,
     "question": "My ancestor is one",
     "answer": "Trainer",
     "description": "That's my grandma, so it's up to me."
   },
   {
     "index": 129,
     "question": "Water that falls from the sky is called?",
     "answer": "Great",
     "description": "It's great that rain can fall from the sky"
   },
   {
     "index": 130,
     "question": "Voltage measurement",
     "answer": "Wow",
     "description": "Well, if you scream waaw it's loud, it means the voltage is high.."
   },
   {
     "index": 131,
     "question": "Animal jumps",
     "answer": "Surprised",
     "description": "If an animal suddenly jumps, it will be shocked"
   },
   {
     "index": 132,
     "question": "Motorcycles can run because the wheels are . .",
     "answer": "Normal",
     "description": "If it's not normal, cube-shaped wheels aren't that normal."
   },
   {
     "index": 133,
     "question": "What habits do bus drivers often do?",
     "answer": "Interest",
     "description": "Yes, if you don't attract your wife and children, what will you eat?"
   },
   {
     "index": 134,
     "question": "If not where is the name",
     "answer": "Match",
     "description": "Ciye if match will not go anywhere"
   },
   {
     "index": 135,
     "question": "Yams &amp; cassava are usually planted by people in…..",
     "answer": "Grave",
     "description": "Can be harvested at the age of 6-8 months"
   },
   {
     "index": 136,
     "question": "Newspapers are called letters……",
     "wrong answer",
     "description": "Why do newspapers write …"
   },
   {
     "index": 137,
     "question": "A person who helps use seat belts and serves us on the plane is called..",
     "answer": "Good people",
     "description": "Yes, the name is a good person, doesn't he like to help."
   },
   {
     "index": 138,
     "question": "Group animals",
     "answer": "Horrible",
     "description": "Most of the time it gets hot in the nest"
   },
   {
     "index": 139,
     "questions": "Those who often score 100 on tests...",
     "answer": "Paper",
     "description": "The value of 100 is on paper right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 140,
     "question": "It's not dry because it's still..",
     "answer": "Vibrate",
     "description": "Yes, the phone doesn't sound dry, that's why it vibrates..."
  },
  {
    "indexes": 141,
     "question": "Andi has ten apples",
     "answer": "Ten",
     "description": "Andi is stingy and doesn't want to give her apples"
   },
   {
     "index": 142,
     "question": "Who can catch criminals at night..",
     "answer": "Proud",
     "description": "It's great to catch criminals, isn't it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 143,
     "question": "Naive vocalist……",
     "answer": "Little",
     "description": "As far as I know David, just a little, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 144,
     "problem": "Eating ketoprak with gado gado is not delicious without…",
     "answer": "Ketelen",
     "description": "Because if you don't get hot you can't feel it"
   },
   {
     "index": 145,
     "question": "An animal that has nine lives is",
     "answer": "Impossible",
     "description": "Because every living thing has only one life"
   },
   {
     "index": 146,
     "question": "Indonesian staple food from ancient times",
     "answer": "Stale",
     "description": "Yeah, old man… people from ancient times"
   },
   {
     "index": 147,
     "question": "There is no …. cracked",
     "answer": "Shard",
     "description": "The name of the glass must be cracked.."
   },
   {
     "index": 148,
     "question": "Usually people take pills because..",
     "answer": "Remember",
     "description": "Can vitamins can be medicine"
   },
   {
     "index": 149,
     "question": "Rice comes from?",
     "answer": "Earth",
     "description": "Rice comes from the earth, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 150,
     "question": "How to stop smoking is?",
     "answer": "Swim",
     "description": "Try it if you don't believe me"
   },
   {
     "index": 151,
     "question": "Dad doesn't want to eat rice anymore because",
     "answer": "Eat",
     "description": "If the rice is already full"
   },
   {
     "index": 152,
     "question": "After eight",
     "answer": "Constipation",
     "description": "Lots of vegetables for smooth digestion"
   },
   {
     "index": 153,
     "question": "If you want to speak English",
     "answer": "Keles",
     "description": "You have to read it, if you can't read it, you can't!"
   },
   {
     "index": 154,
     "question": "Valentino rosi is a racer from",
     "answer": "His mother",
     "description": "If not from the mother then from whom"
   },
   {
     "index": 155,
     "question": "Walk over the river to cross the river..",
     "answer": "Reckless",
     "description": "Cook a walk over the river, why not take the bridge.."
   },
   {
     "index": 156,
     "question": "The candle flame dies if the glass is not covered for lack of it",
     "answer": "Job",
     "description": "The candle is already on, why turn it off"
   },
   {
     "index": 157,
     "question": "Sing in English?",
     "answer": "Rihanna",
     "description": "Have you ever seen Rihana sing Indonesian?"
   },
   {
     "index": 158,
     "problem": "The table has legs …",
     "answer": "Sure",
     "description": "Does a table have legs?"
   },
   {
     "index": 159,
     "question": "Cristiano ronaldo is from?",
     "answer": "Papamama",
     "description": "That's right, cr. ronaldo comes from his father and mother"
   },
   {
     "index": 160,
     "question": "What is the Chinese word for a distended stomach?",
     "answer": "Chachingan",
     "description": "Because a distended stomach has worms"
   },
   {
     "index": 161,
     "question": "1 chicken has 2 legs...a chicken has 2 legs??",
     "answer": "One tail",
     "description": "Focus please focus"
   },
   {
     "index": 162,
     "question": "Drinks that can hold sleep well and are delicious when you usually stay up late",
     "answer": "Again",
     "description": "I'm sure I'll add more if it's delicious"
   },
   {
     "index": 163,
     "question": "People living next door are called..",
     "answer": "Rangga",
     "description": "Yes that's my neighbor"
   },
   {
     "index": 164,
     "question": "Name of the bridge between Surabaya and Madura",
     "answer": "Already exists",
     "description": "Surely the Suramadu bridge already exists"
   },
   {
     "index": 165,
     "question": "Buguru scolded Mamat because… school",
     "answer": "Broken",
     "description": "If you skip school, you will be scolded"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 166,
     "question": "If you are thirsty, drink",
     "answer": "Hold",
     "description": "It's not time for break yet, you'll be scolded by the boss and you can be fired."
   },
   {
     "index": 167,
     "question": "Motor leaks usually at?",
     "answer": "its tires",
     "description": "The motor is leaking tires"
   },
   {
     "index": 168,
     "question": "Don't know why don't",
     "answer": "Sure",
     "description": "If you don't know him, then you don't know who he is"
   },
   {
     "index": 169,
     "question": "Similar and difficult to tell apart because children…",
     "answer": "Komodo",
     "description": "Because dragons are hard to tell apart"
   },
   {
     "index": 170,
     "question": "Before Monday is the day..",
     "answer": "Holidays",
     "description": "Who said it was wrong??"
   },
   {
     "index": 171,
     "question": "Where was I Gusti Ngurah Rai's birthplace?",
     "answer": "Earth",
     "description": "Indonesia is still on earth right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 172,
     "question": "From Bandung to Surabaya we use…",
     "answer": "Pants",
     "description": "When I didn't wear pants from Bandung to Surabaya, I was shy"
   },
   {
     "index": 173,
     "question": "A guy who likes to smile alone is a sign…",
     "answer": "Crazy",
     "description": "Already common symptoms"
   },
   {
     "index": 174,
     "question": "You came late then you",
     "answer": "Congratulations",
     "description": "You've arrived"
   },
   {
     "index": 175,
     "question": "Is there any sugar?",
     "answer": "Glass",
     "description": "Ants eat it if it's not in the glass"
   },
   {
     "index": 176,
     "question": "Usually people die in?",
     "answer": "news",
     "description": "Tell relatives… just been buried"
   },
   {
     "index": 177,
     "problem": "As smart as a squirrel can jump, it will…too",
     "answer": "Road",
     "description": "Cook squirrels can't walk, they're tired…"
   },
   {
     "index": 178,
     "question": "Musical instruments where you can play the strings..",
     "answer": "Berets",
     "description": "Don't swipe it, it'll scratch. It's expensive to buy.."
   },
   {
     "index": 179,
     "question": "What people hacked didn't work?",
     "answer": "Nobody got it",
     "description": "Well yeah that's why it doesn't work right.."
   },
   {
     "index": 180,
     "question": "Big ____ than the pole",
     "answer": "Market",
     "description": "It's true that the market is bigger than the pole.."
   },
   {
     "index": 181,
     "question": "Far in the eyes close in ..",
     "answer": "Here",
     "description": "If you look far away, just be close here"
   },
   {
     "index": 182,
     "question": "Horse legs….",
     "answer": "Sure",
     "description": "Horses do have legs"
   },
   {
     "index": 183,
     "question": "Mom and mom are going to the house because",
     "answer": "Easy",
     "description": "Mom and mom usually go to the house to eat to save money at home"
   },
   {
     "index": 184,
     "question": "Can be pulled but not seen",
     "answer": "Ear",
     "description": "Please try…"
   },
   {
     "index": 185,
     "question": "In biology class",
     "answer": "His son",
     "description": "If not the child then who"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 186,
     "question": "Underarm hair removed",
     "answer": "I am",
     "description": "I was ripped off by someone else"
   },
   {
     "index": 187,
     "question": "I keep waking up….",
     "answer": "Literacy",
     "description": "You must first wake up and open your eyes first"
   },
   {
     "index": 188,
     "question": "Can you sms if there is…",
     "answer": "hplah",
     "description": "If you don't have a cellphone, where can you send SMS"
   },
   {
     "index": 189,
     "question": "What do you do before going to the mosque?",
     "answer": "Parking",
     "description": "Never mind motorbikes...sandals are not allowed in..."
   },
   {
     "index": 190,
     "question": "Lizards like to eat",
     "answer": "Many",
     "description": "You just add more"
   },
   {
     "index": 191,
     "question": "At graduation s1",
     "answer": "Size",
     "description": "Thanksgiving, can pass bachelor degree.."
   },
   {
     "index": 192,
     "question": "Don't watch football",
     "answer": "Gajuga",
     "description": "As long as there's still coffee, it's fine"
   },
   {
     "index": 193,
     "question": "When sleeping people usually..",
     "answer": "Better",
     "description": "Yeah, it's better not sleepy anymore.."
   },
   {
     "index": 194,
     "question": "The pillows are turned over so….",
     "answer": "Cold",
     "description": "If you don't believe me, just try it"
   },
   {
     "index": 195,
     "question": "Vehicles beginning with b ?",
     "answer": "Car",
     "description": "Vehicles beginning with (i) letter b, yes cars …"
   },
   {
     "index": 196,
     "question": "The leader of a village is usually called sir",
     "answer": "No",
     "description": "When you call, you have to turn around"
   },
   {
     "index": 197,
     "question": "There is a father",
     "answer": "Calculate",
     "description": "So that nothing is left behind"
   },
   {
     "index": 198,
     "question": "What is usually on the beach?",
     "answer": "Lips",
     "description": "The seaside is called the shoreline dong"
   },
   {
     "index": 199,
     "question": "Sit equally low",
     "answer": "Leg",
     "description": "It's hard to know with your hands!"
   },
   {
     "index": 200,
     "question": "When someone's birthday is given….",
     "answer": "Yani",
     "description": "Because people have less birthdays"
   },
   {
     "index": 201,
     "question": "Playing tennis using",
     "answer": "Jacket",
     "description": "Because the weather is cold"
   },
   {
     "index": 202,
     "question": "If the child comes home late at night, the parents must...",
     "answer": "True time",
     "description": "If you don't know the time, the child will come home at night in the afternoon"
   },
   {
     "index": 203,
     "question": "Bandung sea?",
     "answer": "Water",
     "description": "Because of the water in the sea"
   },
   {
     "index": 204,
     "question": "To be safe there must be a road car..",
     "answer": "We",
     "description": "If the car runs without us it's called rolling"
   },
   {
     "index": 205,
     "question": "Animals that can?",
     "answer": "Friend",
     "description": "If you fly together with your friends"
   },
   {
     "index": 206,
     "question": "To clean we bathe with",
     "answer": "Sure",
     "description": "If you're not sure it's better not to take a shower"
   },
   {
     "index": 207,
     "question": "If there is fire, there must be…",
     "answer": "Anya",
     "description": "Yes there is an a, if there isn't a then a pi dong"
   },
   {
     "index": 208,
     "question": "Lieonel messi plays soccer in",
     "answer": "Bear",
     "description": "There are so many more…"
   },
   {
     "index": 209,
     "question": "Food tastes bland",
     "answer": "Suggestion",
     "description": "Give suggestions to those who cook, hopefully next time will be better"
   },
   {
     "index": 210,
     "question": "Fasting in the month?",
     "answer": "Distance",
     "description": "Fasting on earth is not good enough, pretending to fast in the month"
   },
   {
     "index": 211,
     "question": "What leaves can be eaten?",
     "answer": "Daunat",
     "description": "It's delicious to eat, especially the chocolate flavor"
   },
   {
     "index": 212,
     "question": "Running distance..",
     "answer": "Go away",
     "description": "If it's close, the name won't run away,"
   },
   {
     "index": 213,
     "question": "Letter?",
     "answer": "abdxt",
     "description": "Those are all letters, correct?"
   },
   {
     "index": 214,
     "question": "When taking a shower, people usually rub…",
     "answer": "Cheek",
     "description": "It's so cute! Isn't it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 215,
     "question": "It's hard to find",
     "answer": "nose",
     "description": "Hey, do you like picking your nose too?"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 216,
     "question": "What a delicious vegetable",
     "answer": "Ludes",
     "description": "Delicious vegetables really run out quickly"
   },
   {
     "index": 217,
     "question": "Clear jam with?",
     "answer": "Lubricant",
     "description": "Just try to get your house fence jammed with lube! it will run smoothly"
   },
   {
     "index": 218,
     "question": "The sound of the jreeng instrument",
     "answer": "Vibrate",
     "description": "When jreeeng… guitar vibrates please…"
   },
   {
     "index": 219,
     "question": "Called not looking",
     "answer": "Rhinoceros",
     "description": "Try calling and you won't see it"
   },
   {
     "index": 220,
     "question": "What are elementary school children most afraid of?",
     "answer": "Injected",
     "description": "Anyone like injections?!"
   },
   {
     "index": 221,
     "question": "Jakarta usually….",
     "answer": "Platb",
     "description": "Because Jakarta's number plate is b, it's usually hot"
   },
   {
     "index": 222,
     "question": "Countries with windmills in…",
     "answer": "Petaada",
     "description": "Really?"
   },
   {
     "index": 223,
     "question": "What do you do when you go to school?",
     "answer": "Request",
     "description": "Huh you kids.."
   },
   {
     "index": 224,
     "question": "Before it becomes rice?",
     "answer": "Hard",
     "description": "Rice is soft, before it's soggy it's hard right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 225,
     "question": "The farmer plants paddy",
     "answer": "Skip",
     "description": "Pa' didi is going to the market like this"
   },
   {
     "index": 226,
     "question": "When you burn a cigarette, it emits",
     "answer": "Child",
     "description": "Smoking in front of a child is not good, so first remove the child from the smoking room"
   },
   {
     "index": 227,
     "question": "What does the cat up the tree do when it comes down first?",
     "answer": "Intention",
     "description": "When there's a will, there's a way!"
   },
   {
     "index": 228,
     "question": "Washing dishes must be with …",
     "answer": "Aware",
     "description": "If you are not aware, the dishes are not washed, they are broken…"
   },
   {
     "index": 229,
     "question": "Mawar met his girlfriend at night at..",
     "answer": "Angry",
     "description": "Grandma said it wasn't good"
   },
   {
     "index": 230,
     "question": "A representative of the people can go to Senayan by using the route..",
     "answer": "Viatol",
     "description": "Now exit the toll road at Semanggi, it's as good as it gets.."
   },
   {
     "index": 231,
     "question": "What is the difference between a motorcycle and a bicycle",
     "answer": "Obviously",
     "description": "You already know the difference with thinking"
   },
   {
     "index": 232,
     "problem": "Teeth stuck in?",
     "answer": "Leg",
     "description": "Ride the motorcycle to change gears on foot"
   },
   {
     "index": 233,
     "question": "The river in Kalimantan",
     "answer": "Many",
     "description": "There are Barito rivers, Kapuas rivers, Kahayan rivers etc."
   },
   {
     "index": 234,
     "question": "Fish breathe with…",
     "answer": "Permission",
     "description": "If you don't allow it, you can't breathe"
   },
   {
     "index": 235,
     "question": "Food is spicy because…",
     "answer": "Manya",
     "description": "Kare name, if cringy tap the name"
   },
   {
     "index": 236,
     "question": "Usually on the side of the road",
     "answer": "Strikeout",
     "description": "That's a no parking sign"
   },
   {
     "index": 237,
     "question": "A good mother should…",
     "answer": "Our Mother",
     "description": "Never be able to repay the kindness"
   },
   {
     "index": 238,
     "question": "An effective medicine for low blood pressure?",
     "answer": "spit",
     "description": "If someone with low blood pressure is spit on, they will immediately have high blood pressure"
   },
   {
     "index": 239,
     "question": "Who the boxer hits",
     "answer": "Relax",
     "description": "Those who hit each other, our boxers, look relaxed"
   },
   {
     "index": 240,
     "question": "What peekaboo can make a baby happy",
     "answer": "Cilokba",
     "description": "Cilook is so cute…."
  },
  {
    "indexes": 240,
      "question": "What peekaboo can make a baby happy",
      "answer": "Cilokba",
      "description": "Cilook is so cute…."
   },
   {
     "index": 241,
     "question": "wind instruments",
     "answer": "Difficult",
     "description": "Playing the flute is difficult"
   },
   {
     "index": 242,
     "question": "Not magic",
     "answer": "Magic",
     "description": "If it's not magic, then it's not magic"
   },
   {
     "index": 243,
     "question": "Astronaut going outside?",
     "answer": "Ganyar",
     "description": "If an astronaut goes away, his family will definitely find him"
   },
   {
     "index": 244,
     "question": "Where we can see the s in the middle",
     "answer": "mattress",
     "description": "Yes yes that's the middle of s right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 245,
     "question": "Which sandals are the best?",
     "answer": "Sandalteration",
     "description": "Well, if you like Swaya, you will like this too!"
   },
   {
     "index": 246,
     "question": "People can stand by",
     "answer": "Strong",
     "description": "If you can't stand how can you stand up"
   },
   {
     "index": 247,
     "question": "What lies at the end of the sea",
     "answer": "Letters",
     "description": "Because the word sea ends with the letter t, it's easy"
   },
   {
     "index": 248,
     "question": "Glass _ _ _ _ . usually found on the streets.",
     "answer": "Ngijo",
     "description": "Protest score minus 50"
   },
   {
     "index": 249,
     "question": "A person with two bodies?",
     "answer": "Wow",
     "description": "If you see a person with two bodies, it will make a scene"
   },
   {
     "index": 250,
     "question": "People draw water in..",
     "answer": "Pour",
     "description": "After neem water must be poured.."
   },
   {
     "index": 251,
     "question": "Open the padlock using….",
     "answer": "Beep",
     "description": "Click as it sounds"
   },
   {
     "index": 252,
     "question": "Usually stored in sacks",
     "answer": "Free",
     "description": "Want rice or sand, just be free"
   },
   {
     "index": 253,
     "question": "The bull butts using..??!",
     "answer": "Power",
     "description": "If you don't use power how can he gore."
   },
   {
     "index": 254,
     "problem": "Prisons can be noisy if all the prisoners",
     "answer": "Cough",
     "description": "Cough must be contagious, right, it's this season"
   },
   {
     "index": 255,
     "question": "What apes that are stepped on don't grumble",
     "answer": "Ceramic",
     "description": "Because it's loud"
   },
   {
     "index": 256,
     "question": "Fences…",
     "answer": "Thank you",
     "description": "Because fences can't eat"
   },
   {
     "index": 257,
     "question": "When we go to the market we usually meet…",
     "answer": "Neighbor",
     "description": "I often meet my ex.."
   },
   {
     "index": 258,
     "question": "Why do people eat with their right hand?",
     "answer": "Because of food",
     "description": "If you use your left hand it's called makiri"
   },
   {
     "index": 259,
     "question": "A painter who can only draw rainbows",
     "answer": "great",
     "description": "Your painter is great.. who the hell is.. rainbows created by god.."
   },
   {
     "index": 260,
     "question": "The back of the tooth is..",
     "answer": "Drummer",
     "description": "Armand Maulana's band is the drummer at the back"
   },
   {
     "index": 261,
     "question": "Can move independently without prompting?",
     "answer": "Collapse",
     "description": "It's called gravity assisted!"
   },
   {
     "index": 262,
     "question": "Unable to enter class",
     "answer": "Flies",
     "description": "Flies disturb students' lessons"
   },
   {
     "index": 263,
     "question": "The kindness of people can be seen from…",
     "answer": "His son",
     "description": "If the child is well cared for, it means he is good"
   },
   {
     "index": 264,
     "question": "Signs that a romantic guy likes…",
     "answer": "Attention",
     "description": "Awesome"
   },
   {
     "index": 265,
     "question": "Everyone breathes through ..?",
     "answer": "Hole",
     "description": "If you don't use a nose hole you can die"
   },
   {
     "index": 266,
     "question": "Rendang is a food that comes from the city we usually call?",
     "answer": "Current",
     "description": "Yeah, we call padang city fluently, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 267,
     "question": "The one driving the ship is called …",
     "answer": "Different",
     "description": "Because there are many people driving the ship"
   },
   {
     "index": 268,
     "problem": "If you are bitten by a spider it could be…",
     "answer": "Body ache",
     "description": "Remember, this is not the world of comics"
   },
   {
     "index": 269,
     "question": "What happens when the car is running?",
     "answer": "The song",
     "description": "So you don't get bored driving right?!"
   },
   {
     "index": 270,
     "question": "Name one example of an animal that walks slowly...",
     "answer": "Wolf",
     "description": "Wolves run fast, if they walk slowly..."
  },
  {
    "indexes": 271,
     "question": "Fowl with 2 legs is",
     "answer": "True",
     "description": "Really?"
   },
   {
     "index": 272,
     "question": "Swiped instrument",
     "answer": "Berets",
     "description": "Duh, if you swipe it becomes a beret, right, honey"
   },
   {
     "index": 273,
     "problem": "No matter how fierce a tiger is, surely it won't eat…",
     "answer": "Avocado",
     "description": "Do tigers really like avocados?"
   },
   {
     "index": 274,
     "question": "Should we swim upstream to ?",
     "answer": "Keair",
     "description": "If you swim, you will definitely be in the water"
   },
   {
     "index": 275,
     "question": "People who work in the hospital?",
     "answer": "Salary",
     "description": "His name is also work.. yes definitely in the salary"
   },
   {
     "index": 276,
     "question": "If we don't wear helmets we get hit",
     "answer": "Panapa",
     "description": "It doesn't matter if it's the other way around, yes why, you get a ticket, for example"
   },
   {
     "index": 277,
     "question": "I keep waking up..",
     "answer": "Literacy",
     "description": "Melek first just take a shower..sageer…"
   },
   {
     "index": 278,
     "question": "Who organizes football matches??",
     "answer": "Time",
     "description": "The rules are 2×45 minutes..normally.."
   },
   {
     "index": 279,
     "question": "3-wheeled vehicle?",
     "answer": "Sure",
     "description": "There are bemo, bajaj, pedicab and others…"
   },
   {
     "index": 280,
     "question": "Indonesian eat",
     "wrong answer",
     "description": "Eat is in English, not Indonesian"
   },
   {
     "index": 281,
     "problem": "The car can't start because of the tires..",
     "answer": "You",
     "description": "If there are a lot of(k) people, you can't pass right..."
   },
   {
     "index": 282,
     "question": "If a goat is skewered, will it be burned?",
     "answer": "Run",
     "description": "What's wrong with the goat, until it's stabbed or burned 🙁"
   },
   {
     "index": 283,
     "question": "Water ripples no sign …",
     "answer": "Calm",
     "description": "If it's quiet, it's quiet, not rippling or noisy."
   },
   {
     "index": 284,
     "question": "A romantic gift for you…",
     "answer": "Applied",
     "description": "Congratulations"
   },
   {
     "index": 285,
     "question": "Delicious dishes typical of Padang",
     "answer": "Kick",
     "description": "Because good food definitely tastes kick"
   },
   {
     "index": 286,
     "question": "To turn on the light we have to press..",
     "answer": "Once",
     "description": "If you die twice, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 287,
     "question": "Would you drink at ?",
     "answer": "Swallow",
     "description": "If you spray it, the shaman"
   },
   {
     "index": 288,
     "question": "The string instrument…",
     "answer": "Beep",
     "description": "There's violin, cello, fiddle and many more"
   },
   {
     "index": 289,
     "question": "Buy medicine at",
     "answer": "Drink",
     "description": "Because what are you going to do if you don't drink it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 290,
     "question": "The most beautiful street in Bandung is the road…",
     "answer": "With you",
     "description": "Wow, that's beautiful"
   },
   {
     "index": 291,
     "question": "Car parked at",
     "answer": "Turn off",
     "description": "If you don't turn off the car runs"
   },
   {
     "index": 292,
     "question": "Young people get girlfriends because they like to play…",
     "answer": "Eye",
     "description": "As long as you don't flirt with other people's boyfriends…."
   },
   {
     "index": 293,
     "question": "I have five balloons",
     "answer": "Duaar",
     "description": "The balloon popped, my heart is so messed up sob sob…"
   },
   {
     "index": 294,
     "question": "Fight mom",
     "answer": "Sin",
     "description": "If you are afraid of sin, don't fight mama's words"
   },
   {
     "index": 295,
     "question": "A contest winner usually gets",
     "answer": "Ridho",
     "description": "If you can't please your parents, you won't win"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 296,
     "question": "Everything will be beautiful in…",
     "answer": "Halno",
     "description": "Not all ends well thoo.."
   },
   {
     "index": 297,
     "problem": "Animals have 6 toes",
     "answer": "Hilarious",
     "description": "Yeah it's cute if you have 6 fingers"
   },
   {
     "index": 298,
     "question": "What is the weirdest animal",
     "answer": "Butterfly",
     "description": "Because at noon you eat rice, at night you drink milk"
   },
   {
     "index": 299,
     "question": "The frog's children are called..",
     "answer": "Family",
     "description": "You have a mother, yes, you have children.."
   },
   {
     "index": 300,
     "question": "Does the water ripple?",
     "answer": "Flat",
     "description": "If it ripples, it must be wavy"
   },
   {
     "index": 301,
     "question": "What box can't be moved",
     "answer": "Penalty",
     "description": "Just try it if you can"
   },
   {
     "index": 302,
     "question": "Apple tastes",
     "answer": "Tired",
     "description": "If you have to be tired at the Bandera ceremony, you should stand up"
   },
   {
     "index": 303,
     "question": "In the sea there are anchovies and fish..",
     "answer": "Cob",
     "description": "And many others"
   },
   {
     "index": 304,
     "question": "People eat because?",
     "answer": "Aware",
     "description": "If you're not aware you can't possibly eat"
   },
   {
     "index": 305,
     "question": "We can see our own face in..",
     "answer": "Sima",
     "description": "There's a photo of us in storage, right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 306,
     "question": "Locations of the 7 wonders of the world….",
     "answer": "Scan",
     "description": "Borobudur is in Jogja, India has the Taj Mahal, and many others"
   },
   {
     "index": 307,
     "question": "The one who leads the country",
     "answer": "There must be",
     "description": "There must be someone who leads the country"
   },
   {
     "index": 308,
     "question": "When an ambulance passes, it usually makes a sound",
     "answer": "Tintinn",
     "description": "If an ambulance passes a crowded place, it will definitely honk"
   },
   {
     "index": 309,
     "question": "Scorpions and snakes live..",
     "answer": "Both",
     "description": "I mentioned scorpions and snakes that's why they're both"
   },
   {
     "index": 310,
     "questions": "Dare because it's right ___ because it's wrong",
     "answer": "No",
     "description": "Wahaha easy right??"
   },
   {
     "index": 311,
     "question": "In a football game",
     "answer": "View",
     "description": "If you can't see why is he guarding the goal?!"
   },
   {
     "index": 312,
     "question": "The turtle is an animal that has..",
     "answer": "Temencewe",
     "description": "Is it okay to have a girl friend, don't be so possessive.."
   },
   {
     "index": 313,
     "question": "Football players that opponents rarely pay attention to..",
     "answer": "Trivial",
     "description": "How can you ignore it, it's so trivial.."
   },
   {
     "index": 314,
     "question": "In order to appear optimally a singer must check..",
     "answer": "Balance",
     "description": "So there's no burden to sing, you've already paid for it.."
   },
   {
     "index": 315,
     "question": "Far in the eyes close in",
     "answer": "Here",
     "description": "If you are far away, just come here"
   },
   {
     "index": 316,
     "question": "Fast motorcycle or bicycle",
     "answer": "Car",
     "description": "Yeah obviously a faster car right"
   },
   {
     "index": 317,
     "question": "Ring is worn on the finger",
     "answer": "Login",
     "description": "Yes, if you don't enter, you can't use it"
   },
   {
     "index": 318,
     "question": "What we wear when it rains..",
     "answer": "Honey",
     "description": "If you get wet in the rain, it's a shame because it's wet"
   },
   {
     "index": 319,
     "question": "Animal stuck to the wall?",
     "answer": "Tired",
     "description": "Just walking is tiring, let alone sticking…"
   },
   {
     "index": 320,
     "question": "If you were surrounded by 20 lions what would you do?",
     "answer": "Relax",
     "description": "It's just the tail"
   },
   {
     "index": 321,
     "question": "People are cold",
     "answer": "Remotac",
     "description": "The ac temperature on the remote is 16°c, the cat just gets cold."
   },
   {
     "index": 322,
     "question": "Upin's friend??",
     "answer": "Ijat",
     "description": "Because of his sister's grandfather"
   },
   {
     "index": 323,
     "question": "Farmers hoeing to ?",
     "answer": "Bottom",
     "description": "There really is a hoe up"
   },
   {
     "index": 324,
     "question": "Elephant only in",
     "answer": "Rear",
     "description": "Because the elephant is on the back"
   },
   {
     "index": 325,
     "question": "In physics, a solid to a liquid is called a process..",
     "answer": "Pawnshop",
     "description": "Need funds fast? 30 minutes straight cash!"
   },
   {
     "index": 326,
     "question": "Ani drew the same triangle",
     "answer": "Kiki",
     "description": "Because I'm working in a group"
   },
   {
     "index": 327,
     "question": "Not voting during elections",
     "answer": "Gaasik",
     "description": "Elections determine the fate of the nation, not voting isn't fun"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 328,
     "question": "Hot feet from being hit",
     "answer": "Lpotnya",
     "description": "Heat hit the exhaust"
   },
   {
     "index": 329,
     "question": "Thieves usually steal at…",
     "answer": "quiet",
     "description": "If it's loud, you'll be caught"
   },
   {
     "index": 330,
     "question": "The police arranged the road then …..",
     "answer": "Current",
     "description": "After arranging the road, it's smooth sailing"
   },
   {
     "index": 331,
     "question": "A little – a little longer so..",
     "answer": "Many",
     "description": "If you add a little, it will make a lot"
   },
   {
     "index": 332,
     "question": "……..behind the rock",
     "answer": "Uutab",
     "description": "That's right, if you turn it upside down you'll turn to stone"
   },
   {
     "index": 333,
     "question": "There are ants there",
     "answer": "Enya",
     "description": "If you don't have e, then smut"
   },
   {
     "index": 334,
     "question": "People who rarely go anywhere are called?",
     "answer": "Goalkeeper",
     "description": "If you concede goals anywhere, please!"
   },
   {
     "index": 335,
     "question": "The world is not as wide as a leaf??",
     "answer": "Correct",
     "description": "Because the world is not as wide as a leaf"
   },
   {
     "index": 336,
     "question": "Abbreviation of land",
     "answer": "Sda",
     "description": "That's right! land, air, and water are natural resources (natural resources)"
   },
   {
     "index": 337,
     "question": "Grass-eating animals",
     "answer": "Poor",
     "description": "I'm sorry you're eating grass and making it into satay again..."
   },
   {
     "index": 338,
     "question": "How fast is the motor?",
     "answer": "The bolt",
     "description": "If you don't fasten the body, what do you do?"
   },
   {
     "index": 339,
     "question": "The horse-drawn vehicle..",
     "answer": "Gaaman",
     "description": "Because it is pulled by a horse the vehicle can get into an accident"
   },
   {
     "index": 340,
     "question": "Tarzan's friend..",
     "answer": "You",
     "description": "You look like a monkey, so do I…"
   },
   {
     "index": 341,
     "question": "What did dad do during Ramadan",
     "answer": "Work",
     "description": "Because it's not time for a holiday yet"
   },
   {
     "index": 342,
     "question": "Before God created nature. God created?",
     "answer": "Vetyvera",
     "description": "Vetyvera is nature's older sister, of course it goes first"
   },
   {
     "index": 343,
     "problem": "Living things that have a supply of water",
     "answer": "Camel",
     "description": "…"
   },
   {
     "index": 344,
     "question": "20 divided by 2 counts…",
     "answer": "Alms",
     "description": "20 divided by 2 counts as alms"
   },
   {
     "index": 345,
     "question": "Elephants die, leave them..",
     "answer": "Dangnya",
     "description": "Leave the cage, if in the forest leave the forest.."
  },
  {
    "indexes": 346,
     "question": "Unable to save the book in…",
     "answer": "Sir",
     "description": "Dimas borrowed his book yesterday afternoon"
   },
   {
     "index": 347,
     "question": "Items that can be borrowed",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "If it's not there, it can't be borrowed"
   },
   {
     "index": 348,
     "question": "Lizards usually eat?",
     "answer": "Hmmm",
     "description": "That's how it sounds"
   },
   {
     "index": 349,
     "question": "Rain falls from..",
     "answer": "Evening",
     "description": "Because asr has not come yet"
   },
   {
     "index": 350,
     "question": "When will you blow the flute?",
     "answer": "Wet",
     "description": "Just try to hold your flute when it's blown.."
   },
   {
     "index": 351,
     "question": "Most people sleep at night",
     "answer": "Merem",
     "description": "If you don't brake, you won't sleep"
   },
   {
     "index": 352,
     "question": "The egg or the chicken first",
     "answer": "Adam",
     "description": "Because first the prophet adam in the world before the chicken and the egg"
   },
   {
     "index": 353,
     "question": "Sunday is also called a date?",
     "answer": "No",
     "description": "If the day, then the day, if the date, then the date"
   },
   {
     "index": 354,
     "question": "When fighting soldiers carry..",
     "answer": "The shoes",
     "description": "If it hurts, my leg hurts.."
   },
   {
     "index": 355,
     "question": "A chicken is called ….",
     "answer": "Satiety",
     "description": "Well, dina eats chicken, it makes you full"
   },
   {
     "index": 356,
     "question": "Bring a car must bring",
     "answer": "One",
     "description": "How about if you bring two...?!?!"
   },
   {
     "index": 357,
     "question": "After ….. waste is thrown away",
     "answer": "Eat",
     "description": "Yes..if you eat it, throw it away"
   },
   {
     "index": 358,
     "question": "Motorcycles have wheels",
     "answer": "Yes",
     "description": "Obviously the motorbike has wheels, if you don't have it you can't run it"
   },
   {
     "index": 359,
     "question": "The wheel is always….",
     "answer": "Colored",
     "description": "There is no wheel without color"
   },
   {
     "index": 360,
     "question": "On highways there are usually..",
     "answer": "Light",
     "description": "If there's no light, you won't see it..."
   },
   {
     "index": 361,
     "question": "In addition to tug of war, residents celebrate the 17th with?",
     "answer": "Pray a prayer",
     "description": "Because I'm blessed"
   },
   {
     "index": 362,
     "question": "String instrument",
     "answer": "Normal",
     "description": "Because it is common in the market"
   },
   {
     "index": 363,
     "question": "The coffee shop is called…",
     "answer": "Times",
     "description": "Hohoho, it's nice to have coffee on the side in the afternoon.."
   },
   {
     "index": 364,
     "question": "Camels live in…",
     "answer": "Nature",
     "description": "Indeed all living things live in nature"
   },
   {
     "index": 365,
     "question": "What is a name for someone who has taken then left",
     "answer": "Former",
     "description": "Because the ex is a thief of hearts that hurts then leaves"
   },
   {
     "index": 366,
     "question": "Rice has become",
     "answer": "Thanks",
     "description": "If the rice is ready, you should be grateful"
   },
   {
     "index": 367,
     "questions": "What students often bring to see and read",
     "answer": "Chapterv",
     "description": "Chapter five is in every textbook"
   },
   {
     "index": 368,
     "question": "Pak rt can fly",
     "answer": "Ticket",
     "description": "If you want to fly by plane, you must have a ticket"
   },
   {
     "index": 369,
     "question": "What do you do when you drink coffee?",
     "answer": "Sruput",
     "description": "To make the coffee taste better, isn't it!"
   },
   {
     "index": 370,
     "question": "On the last lap, Rossi cut the marquest for sure….",
     "answer": "Kungan",
     "description": "The greatest Rossi around the corner ."
   },
   {
     "index": 371,
     "question": "Prambanan Temple is a relic from the past..",
     "answer": "Previously",
     "description": "Now no one builds temples anymore"
   },
   {
     "index": 372,
     "question": "The child is absent from school because…",
     "answer": "Outside",
     "description": "If he is in the palace, it means he is going to school"
   },
   {
     "index": 373,
     "question": "A friend who helped Batman against 50 enemies was?",
     "answer": "Resting",
     "description": "It's a hassle for 50 enemies….ouch.."
   },
   {
     "index": 374,
     "question": "merlion statue is in",
     "answer": "Place",
     "description": "Dong place please, when the statue is traveling"
   },
   {
     "index": 375,
     "question": "Fish breathe with",
     "answer": "Calm down",
     "description": "If you stutter you could die"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 376,
     "question": "Motor crashed because",
     "answer": "Galiath",
     "description": "Because there is a dig in front of him, he digs.. yes falls"
   },
   {
     "index": 377,
     "question": "People die because of loss…",
     "answer": "Breath",
     "description": "The time when people die of breath"
   },
   {
     "index": 378,
     "question": "If the ant is small",
     "answer": "Animals",
     "description": "I'm not wrong right?"
   },
   {
     "index": 379,
     "question": "The color of the flag is….",
     "answer": "Only two",
     "description": "When is it tricolor?"
   },
   {
     "index": 380,
     "question": "Real madrid's number 11",
     "answer": "Bule",
     "description": "Actually, Gareth Bale is a foreigner. Why is that difficult?"
   },
   {
     "index": 381,
     "question": "There is a king",
     "answer": "Orphan",
     "description": "The father died 🙁"
   },
   {
     "index": 382,
     "question": "Tea is iced so",
     "answer": "Fresh",
     "description": "Especially in hot weather"
   },
   {
     "index": 383,
     "question": "We see stars in..",
     "answer": "Shoulders",
     "description": "On the shoulders of the general, that rank, you know..."
   },
   {
     "index": 384,
     "problem": "Foot stepped on the glass….",
     "answer": "Eye",
     "description": "Well I can't see…the glasses are broken…"
   },
   {
     "index": 385,
     "question": "Can you eat spinach?",
     "answer": "Toploe",
     "description": "Bener2 top, I'm just weak when I'm just spinach"
   },
   {
     "index": 386,
     "question": "Amazing action",
     "answer": "Whistle",
     "description": "That's amazing.."
   },
   {
     "index": 387,
     "question": "How to add friends in seconds",
     "answer": "Nembakgirl",
     "description": "If you are rejected, you will definitely say that we are just friends..poor"
   },
   {
     "index": 388,
     "question": "What often bothers people when they want to do good?",
     "answer": "Naughty",
     "description": "How come you want to do good when you are disturbed? It's really naughty, isn't it?"
   },
   {
     "index": 389,
     "question": "If you want to go to a wedding party",
     "answer": "Anrapi",
     "description": "I see, that's neat handsome"
   },
   {
     "index": 390,
     "question": "A tree that grows after the fasting month",
     "answer": "Sorry",
     "description": "I'm sorry to be born and inner heart"
   },
   {
     "index": 391,
     "question": "There are eleven sheep in the truck",
     "answer": "Eleven",
     "description": "You just jump, don't run away"
   },
   {
     "index": 392,
     "question": "Free traffic jam",
     "answer": "Top",
     "description": "Means the toll road must be top"
   },
   {
     "index": 393,
     "question": "Those who help doctors…",
     "answer": "Cured",
     "description": "The one who helps the doctor, God willing, he will recover.."
   },
   {
     "index": 394,
     "question": "Beach in Jakarta?",
     "answer": "Abss",
     "description": "Too long gone because of waste, sad"
   },
   {
     "index": 395,
     "question": "Animals that can change the color of their skin",
     "answer": "Advanced",
     "description": "(chameleon) because animals that can change color are sophisticated, right!"
  },
  {
    "indexes": 396,
     "question": "What do thieves usually do on Saturday nights and Sundays",
     "answer": "Wash",
     "description": "The problem is the clothes smell, because on Friday night Saturday to run chased by residents"
   },
   {
     "index": 397,
     "question": "Animals that perch on food",
     "answer": "Hungry",
     "description": "Yes, because I'm hungry"
   },
   {
     "index": 398,
     "question": "United we stand, divided we…",
     "answer": "Split",
     "description": "If you are divorced, you will definitely separate"
   },
   {
     "index": 399,
     "question": "Jakarta has traffic jams…. passing by",
     "answer": "App",
     "description": "Jakarta is jammed, are you ready to pass??"
   },
   {
     "index": 400,
     "question": "People who often come to campus",
     "answer": "Still alive",
     "description": "Yes, if you're dead, you can't go to campus"
   },
   {
     "index": 401,
     "question": "In one year…..month",
     "answer": "Only one",
     "description": "Even if you wait five years, the number of months is still one."
   },
   {
     "index": 402,
     "question": "After high school graduation",
     "answer": "Go home",
     "description": "Go home…give news to your parents, congratulations!"
   },
   {
     "index": 403,
     "question": "A deer has..",
     "answer": "Friend",
     "description": "He has so many friends that he has even more…"
   },
   {
     "index": 404,
     "question": "Japanese ninja cartoon",
     "answer": "Watch",
     "description": "Because cartoons are fun"
   },
   {
     "index": 405,
     "question": "Agus wants to play football at...",
     "answer": "Allow",
     "description": "Allowed by the parents, otherwise agus will cry later"
   },
   {
     "index": 406,
     "question": "What animal is good at predicting the weather",
     "answer": "Tiger",
     "description": "Rain tiger, hot tiger, dark tiger at night.."
   },
   {
     "index": 407,
     "question": "What ball looks like a cat?",
     "answer": "Bolaemon",
     "description": "Hey bamboo propellers"
   },
   {
     "index": 408,
     "question": "Who drives the train….",
     "answer": "Masagus",
     "description": "Mas Agus is my neighbor, you know…."
   },
   {
     "index": 409,
     "question": "Long distance running",
     "answer": "Unfortunate",
     "description": "It's far away, it's not hot yet.."
   },
   {
     "index": 410,
     "question": "Don't forget when you sleep",
     "answer": "Build",
     "description": "If you don't wake up it could be bad"
   },
   {
     "index": 411,
     "question": "What gorilla is as big as a building?",
     "answer": "oversized",
     "description": "Where there is a gorilla that is as big as a building…."
   },
   {
     "index": 412,
     "question": "A little bit longer so….",
     "answer": "Little",
     "description": "It's a little bit so take it a little bit"
   },
   {
     "index": 413,
     "question": "Mr. police ticket the violators with?",
     "answer": "Prior",
     "description": "If you don't pay attention, don't step aside, the violators will"
  }
]